Guide to the Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
- Asher, Eric, The Roommate, Greenleaf Classics, PR 312, 1971 (Box 47)
- Austin, Drew, Queer Pen, P. E. C., FL 46, 1968 (Box 51)
- Avery, Everett, Road Boys, Rough Trade, RT 470, n.d. (Box 56)
- Baker, Tex, Little Meat Suckers, Rough Trade, RT 455, n.d. (Box 55)
- Baldwin, Dick, Hunk!, Hamilton House, RAM 10-104, 1974 (Box 32)
- Baldwin, Dick, Naked Danger, Hamilton House, RAM 10-118, 1975 (Box 33)
- Ballard, Jess, Mostly Male, Cameo Library, CC-166, 1974 (Box 13)
- Bandridge, Guy, Oh Counselor!, Guild Press Ltd., RC 110, 1971 (Box 28)
- Banis, Victor J., The Why Not, Greenleaf Classics, GC 209, 1966 (Box 24)
- Banner, Henry, Wild Paths To Choose, Private Editions Books, PE 385, 1966 (Box 49)
- Barber, Sonny, Live One, F.S. Publishing, GPL 102, n.d. (Box 17)
- Barker, Sonny, Shafter, Phenix Publishers, PR 274, 1970 (Box 46)
- Barker, Sonny, Vampire's Kiss, Phenix Publishers, PR 278, 1970 (Box 46)
- Barker, Sonny, Beautiful Bumpkin, Phenix Publishers, PR 282, 1970 (Box 46)
- Barnes, Gregory, Homo Alley, All Star Books, AS 46, 1965 (Box 1)
- Baron, Bruce, Hard Boys for Teachers, Star Distributors, Ltd., WB109, 1975 (Box 90)
- Baron, Milt, Hard Truckin' Sucker, Rough Trade, RT 444, n.d. (Box 55)
- Barr, James, Quatrefoil, Paperback Library, 54-871, 1965 (Box 41)
- Barr, James, The Occasional Man, Paperback Library, 54-918, 1966 (Box 41)
- Barron, Tony, Angelo, Monkey Pubn., -0-, 1969 (Box 36)
- Barrow, L. Jay, "Hollywood-Gay Capitol...", Triumph, TNC 139, 1968 (Box 87)
- Barrow, Ricky, Crew Boy, Star Dist., WB 107, 1975 (Box 67)
- Barrows, Philip, Whores, Queers & Others, Greenleaf Classics, GC 261, 1967 (Box 24)
- Barrows, Philip, Whores, Queers & Others Vol 1, Olympia Press, TC-211, 1967 (Box 39)
- Barrows, Philip, Whores, Queers & Others Vol 2, Olympia Press, TC-212, 1967 (Box 39)
- Barry, Jebb, Country Boys, Star Dist., WB 105, 1975 (Box 67)
- Bart, Carl, The Preacher's Lust, Star Dist., HB 502, 1977 (Box 62)
- Bart, Carl, Leather & Sex, Star Dist., HS 505, 1977 (Box 62)
- Bart, L. K., Backdoor Slave, Rough Trade, RT 446, n.d. (Box 55)
- Bart, L. K., Cock Cruisers, Rough Trade, RT 456, n.d. (Box 55)
- Bart, L.K., Playground Prey, Star Dist., SS-1008, 1976 (Box 66)
- Barton, Carl, Private Dick, Star Dist., SS-1016, 1977 (Box 66)
- Barton, Lee W., Tricks Hot, Tricks Cold, Greenleaf Classics, GL 119, 1969 (Box 25)
- Bartrand, Franklin, Pipeline, Blueboy Library, 80015, 1976 (Box 7)
- Bartrand, Franklin, Savage Conquest, Blueboy Library, 80030, 1977 (Box 8)
- Bartrand, Franklin, Pharoah's Champion, Blueboy Library, 80042, 1977 (Box 8)
- Bates, Norman, Teen Analism '70, Barclay House, 7073, 1969 (Box 6)
- Bates, William Astor, Mancorps, Surrey House, HIS 06964, 1973 (Box 71)
- Baxt, George, A Queer Kind of Death, Signet Books, P3188, 1967 (Box 95)
- Baxter, Don, Streetwise And Horny, Arena, DS 109, 1982 (Box 1)
- Baxter, Don, Island Meat, Arena, DS 113, 1982 (Box 1)
- Baxter, Don, His Big Brother, Arena, DS 119, 1983 (Box 1)
- Baxter, Paul, Sexual Espionage, Numbers, 10020, 1978 (Box 37)
- Baxter, Shane V., The Sultry Stud, Greenleaf Classics, GL 128, 1969 (Box 26)
- Becker, Wim, Growing Up Hard, Surrey House, MH 415, 1973 (Box 81)
- Beech, James, Sailor Boy, Rough Trade, RT 457, n.d. (Box 55)
- Belaire, Jim, Young Tim, 101 Enterprises, 101-10, 1968 (Box 40)
- Bender, Barry, Cock Cousins, Surrey House, MH 442, 1974 (Box 82)
- Bender, Trock, The Gay Force, Central Sales Ltd., V.B.-101, 1969 (Box 88)
- Benderson, Bruce, Kyle, Star Dist., CC-101, n.d. (Box 59)
- Bennett, P. H., Choice Beef, Surree Ltd, HIS 69256, 1978 (Box 77)
- Bennett, P. H., Halfbreed, Surree Ltd, HIS 69260, 1978 (Box 77)
- Bennett, P. H., Squaw Man, Surree Ltd, HIS 69245, 1978 (Box 77)
- Bennett, P. H., Secret Trade, Surree Ltd, HIS 69265, 1978 (Box 78)
- Bennett, P. H., Trucker's Trick, Surree Ltd, HIS 69267, 1978 (Box 78)
- Bennett, P. H., Chicken Lover, Surree Ltd, HIS 69282, 1979 (Box 78)
- Bennett, P. H., Trappin' Man, Surree Ltd, HIS 69280, 1979 (Box 78)
- Bennett, P. H., Trappin' Man Ii, Surree Ltd, HIS 69402, 1979 (Box 78)
- Bennett, P. H., Halfbreed's Rise, Surree Ltd, HIS 69404, 1979 (Box 78)
- Bennett, P. H., Trappin' Man Iii, Surree Ltd, HIS 69406, 1980 (Box 79)
- Bennett, P. H., Dark Master, Surree Ltd, MH 485, 1978 (Box 83)
- Bennett, P. H., His Master's Meat, Surree Ltd, SS 054, 1979 (Box 86)
- Benson, Dave, Black Stud: White Slave, Star Distributors, Ltd., BD1005, 1976 (Box 90)
- Bent, William, No Holds Barred, XXX Inc., GW 133, n.d. (Box 19)
- Benton, Josh, Teen Buddies, Surey Books, SSS 130, 1982 (Box 87)
- Benton, Josh, Jackin' Buddies, Surey Books, HIS 69436, 1981 (Box 80)
- Benton, Josh, Teen Tonguer, Surrey House, HIS 69118, 1974 (Box 72)
- Benton, Josh, High School Studs, Surrey Ltd, SSS 109, 1981 (Box 86)
- Benton, Riley, The Dungaree Jungle, All Star Books, AS 88, 1966 (Box 1)
- Bernard, Stuart, Chicken Delight, Rough Trade, RT 429, 1975 (Box 55)
- Berns, Mike, His Uncle's Boy, Star Dist., WB 108, 1975 (Box 67)
- Billings, John, Roommates And Lovers, Timely Books, -0-, 1971 (Box 87)
- Bistroff, Ted., Massage Parlor Stud, Surree Ltd, HIS 69237, 1978 (Box 77)
- Blake, Vic, Getting The Shaft, GX, Inc., TC 215, n.d. (Box 30)
- Blake, Vic, Getting The Shaft, Publisher's Consultants, LR 106, 1977 (Box 50)
- Bolin, Jamie, The Meat Eaters, Star Dist., SPADE 120, 1973 (Box 65)
- Bond, Harlon, Ranch House Stud, Greenleaf Classics, AC 141, 1976 (Box 21)
- Bonds, Jason, Shaft A Virgin Stud, Greenleaf Classics, AC 261, 1981 (Box 23)
- Bonds, Jason, Macho Stud, Greenleaf Classics, AC 268, 1982 (Box 23)
- Bonds, Jason, Hustling Stud, Greenleaf Classics, AC 271, 1982 (Box 23)
- Bonds, Jason, Chicken Coming Out, Greenleaf Classics, AC 274, 1982 (Box 23)
- Bonds, Jason, Bourban Street Studs, Greenleaf Classics, AC 275, 1982 (Box 23)
- Bonds, Jason, Midday Cowboy, Greenleaf Classics, AC 278, 1982 (Box 23)
- Bonds, Jason, Blow The Man Down, Greenleaf Classics, AC 282, 1982 (Box 23)
- Bonds, Jason, Up Yours, Buddy!, Greenleaf Classics, AC 298, 1983 (Box 23)
- Bonds, Jason, F-F Brothers, Greenleaf Classics, AC 299, 1983 (Box 23)
- Bone, I. L., Boy Whore, Spade Publishing, SP-104, n.d. (Box 58)
- Bookman, Sidney, Homo, Continental Classics, CC-318, 1969 (Box 14)
- Booton, Morris, Tearoom Dangler, Surrey House, HIS 06917, 1972 (Box 69)
- Bortner, Jadkle, The Good Fairy, Greenleaf Classics, GL 110, 1969 (Box 25)
- Bowie, Joe D., Half World, Kozy Books, Inc., K 167, 1962 (Box 33)
- Boysen, Roger, Hot Hole Hustler, Star Dist., WB 103, 1975 (Box 67)
- Brace, Jack, Hustling Stud, Gay World Special, -0-, n.d. (Box 19)
- Branch, Carl, A Few Of The Boys, Greenleaf Classics, AB 434, 1968 (Box 20)
- Branch, Carl, Idylls Of The Queens, Greenleaf Classics, AB 439, 1968 (Box 20)
- Branch, Carl, All Shades Of Gay, Greenleaf Classics, AB 441, 1968 (Box 20)
- Breaker, Dan, Virgin Boy, Grand Prix Classics, -0-, n.d. (Box 19)
- Breaker, Dan, Midnight Marine, Grand Prix Classics, -0-, n.d. (Box 90)
- Brent, Lynton Wright, The Gay Bunch, Anchor Publications, WL 112, 1965 (Box 1)
- Brent, Lynton Wright, Sir Gay, Brentwood, BL 101, 1965 (Box 11)
- Brett, Chuck, Roughneck Rimmer, Rough Trade, RT 412, n.d. (Box 54)
- Brett, Chuck, The Coach's Boy, Rough Trade, RT 418, n.d. (Box 54)
- Brewster, Ken, Sweetass Little Brother, Rough Trade, RT 425, n.d. (Box 54)
- Bright, Len, Play Gay, Utopia Publications, AH 139, 1974 (Box 88)
- Bright, Lynwood, The Men Between, Private Editions Books, PE 375, 1966 (Box 48)
- Brink, Alex, Gay Relations, N. P. Inc., 1046, 1970 (Box 36)
- Britain, Sloane, Insatiable, Midwood, 57, 1960 (Box 34)
- Bronson, Wolfe, Tall Timber, Hamilton House, RAM 10-101, 1974 (Box 32)
- Bronson, Wolfe, Truck Stop, Hamilton House, RAM 10-105, 1974 (Box 32)
- Brooks, Adrian, The Glass Arcade, Pocket Books, 82916-5, 1980 (Box 48)
- Brooks, Franklin, Dirt Road Deliverance, Greenleaf Classics, AC 284, 1982 (Box 23)
- Brown, L. J., The Queens Are In The Parlor, Greenleaf Classics, AB 432, 1968 (Box 20)
- Brown, Pierce, Mixed Nuts, GX, Inc., SP 105, 1971 (Box 29)
- Brown, Warren, The Fag Chaser, P. E. C., FL 86, 1970 (Box 52)
- Browne, Jim, Cycle Sadist, Star Dist., SS-1021, 1979 (Box 66)
- Browning, Jimmy, Dick Jockey, Surrey House, HIS 69109, 1974 (Box 72)
- Bruce, Edmund, Ride to Hell, Neva Paperbacks, Inc., 817, 1968 (Box 95)
- Brunner, Ace, Highway Hustler, Surrey House, HIS 06911, 1971 (Box 69)
- Bryan, Dan, Hard Hat Fucker, Star Dist., SS-1024, 1979 (Box 67)
- Bryan, Dan, Trucker Stud, Star Dist., SS-1026, 1979 (Box 67)
- Bteven, Brooks, The Hung Roommate, Star Dist., SPADE 135, 1973 (Box 66)
- Butler, L., Trick Trip, Gay Parisian Press, GPP 100, 1970 (Box 19)
- Butler, L., The Boy Peddler, Gay Parisian Press, GPP 103, 1970 (Box 19)
- Butler, L., One Final Orgy, Gay Parisian Press, GPP 108, 1970 (Box 19)
- Butler, L., Money Gay, Gay Parisian Press, GPP 109, 1970 (Box 19)
- Butler, L., Gay Realization, Gay Parisian Press, GP, n.d. (Box 19)
- Cain, James M., Serenade, Signet Books, 1153, 1937 (Box 58)
- Caldwell, Clay, Very Close Friends, Blueboy Library, 80013, 1976 (Box 7)
- Caldwell, Clay, Top Man, Blueboy Library, 80027, 1977 (Box 8)
- Caldwell, Clay, The Jocks, Blueboy Library, 80033, 1977 (Box 8)
- Caldwell, Clay, Asphalt Cowboys, Blueboy Library, 80056, 1977 (Box 9)
- Caldwell, Clay, Wrestler Student, Blueboy Library, NIL 112, 1978 (Box 37)
- Caldwell, Clay, Trucker's Tail, Surey Books, HIS 69450, 1982 (Box 80)
- Caldwell, Clay, Workin' Out, Surey Books, HIS 69458, 1983 (Box 80)
- Caldwell, Clay, Growing Up, Surey Books, SSS 117, 1981 (Box 86)
- Caldwell, Clay, Tailpipe Trucker, Surree Ltd, HIS 69147, 1975 (Box 73)
- Caldwell, Clay, Camp Buddies, Surree Ltd, HIS 69250, 1978 (Box 77)
- Caldwell, Clay, Service, Stud, Surree Ltd, HIS 69258, 1978 (Box 77)
- Caldwell, Clay, College Stud Rape, Surree Ltd, HIS 69259, 1978 (Box 77)
- Caldwell, Clay, S & M Truckers, Surree Ltd, HIS 69264, 1978 (Box 78)
- Caldwell, Clay, Stud-Camp Tricks, Surree Ltd, HIS 69271, 1978 (Box 78)
- Caldwell, Clay, Victim Of Vice, Surree Ltd, HIS 69279, 1979 (Box 78)
- Caldwell, Clay, Horny Studs' Ranch, Surree Ltd, HIS 69401, 1979 (Box 78)
- Caldwell, Clay, Pledge-Slave, Surree Ltd, HIS 69419, 1980 (Box 79)
- Caldwell, Clay, Makin' The Team, Surree Ltd, HIS 69429, 1981 (Box 79)
- Caldwell, Clay, Humpin' Hayloft Cousins, Surey Books, HIS 69440, 1981 (Box 80)
- Calhoun, Roy, Campus Porn Stars, Star Dist., AGR 172, 1987 (Box 68)
- Calhoun, Roy, Interstate Studs, Surey Books, HIS 69562, 1987 (Box 80)
- Calvano, Tony, Under Five Fags, Greenleaf Classics, AB 449, 1968 (Box 20)
- Calvano, Tony, The Fairy Goddess, Phenix Publishers, CB 561, 1968 (Box 43)
- Calvano, Tony, Roll Call In Sodom, Phenix Publishers, LL 776, 1968 (Box 44)
- Cameron, Bruce, The Case Against Colonel Sutton, Paperback Library, 54-266, 1961 (Box 41)
- Campbell, Lloyd, Lighthouse Is For Loving, GX, Inc., TC 204, n.d. (Box 29)
- Cannon, Tony, Mountain Stud, Hamilton House, RAM 10-108, 1974 (Box 32)
- Cannon, Tony, Hustler, Hamilton House, RAM 10-115, 1975 (Box 33)
- Cantley, Adrian, A Shot in the Corral, Numbers, NIL-103, 1978 (Box 90)
- Capote, Truman, A Tree Of Night, Signet Books, 878, 1945 (Box 57)
- Capote, Truman, The Grass Harp, Signet Books, 1020, 1951 (Box 57)
- Capote, Truman, The Grass Harp & Tree Of Night, Signet Books, D 1884, 1945 (Box 58)
- Capote, Truman, The Grass Harp & Tree Of Night, Signet Books, S 1333, 1945 (Box 58)
- Capote, Truman, Breakfast At Tiffany's, Signet Books, D 1727, 1958 (Box 58)
- Carco, Francis, Perversity, Berkley, Y623, 1928 (Box 11)
- Carey, Jim, Party Boy, Parisian Press, P 221, 1972 (Box 42)
- Carey, Mike, Hollywood Delivery Boy!, Gay Parisian Press, GP, 1971 (Box 19)
- Carey, Mike, Pool Boy, Parisian Press, P 201, 1971 (Box 41)
- Carmichael, K.C., The Snake And The Womb, Brandon House, 2050, 1968 (Box 12)
- Carney, William, A Year In A Closet, Warner Books, 0-446-78196-7, 1974 (Box 88)
- Carpenter, Lee, The Hungry Boyfriend, Star Dist., Club 101, 1973 (Box 59)
- Carruthers, R. C., Adam And Adam, Echelon, IL-228, 1967 (Box 15)
- Carter, Ben, Sixty Nine Gay Street, P. E. C., FL 22, 1967 (Box 51)
- Carter, David, The Iron Game, David Carter, -0-, 1976 (Box 13)
- Carter, Dr., My Gay Diary, Bark Book, -0-, 1969 (Box 6)
- Carter, Floyd, The Story Of '9', 101 Enterprises, 101-18, 1967 (Box 40)
- Carter, Floyd, One A Night, 101 Enterprises, 101-22, 1967 (Box 40)
- Carter, Floyd, Camp Butch, 101 Enterprises, 101-17, 1968 (Box 40)
- Carter, Floyd, Big Joe, 101 Enterprises, 101-21, 1968 (Box 40)
- Carter, Floyd, Forbidden Fruit, 101 Enterprises, 101-36, 1968 (Box 40)
- Carter, Mike, New Meat, Brandon House, 6089, 1969 (Box 13)
- Carter, Vic, Things Never Went Right..., XXX Inc., GW 131, n.d. (Box 18)
- Caruso, Joe, Queer Hustler, Neva Paperbacks, 743-S, 1965 (Box 36)
- Caruthers, Remi, Queen's Castle, P. E. C., FL 93, 1970 (Box 52)
- Case, Curry, 69th St. Super, Eros Publishing, IGL-1, 1971 (Box 16)
- Case, Curry, Hustling Hackie, Eros Publishing, IGL-2, 1971 (Box 16)
- Case, Curry, Boy At The "Y", Eros Publishing, IGL-3, 1971 (Box 16)
- Case, Curry, Provincetown Playboy, Eros Publishing, IGL-4, 1971 (Box 16)
- Case, Ensan, Wing-Men, Avon, 0-380-47647-9-250, 1979 (Box 4)
- Cassidy, H. A., Super Spur, GX, Inc., SP 103, 1972 (Box 28)
- Cassidy, Will *, The Gang Rape, Star Dist., SPADE 101, 1972 (Box 65)
- Cassidy, Will, The Blue-Eyed Stud, Star Dist., SPADE 128, 1973 (Box 65)
- Caulder, Thorpe, Headlines For Johnny, Greenleaf Classics, GC 351, 1968 (Box 24)
- Chadwick, Stu, Weekend At The "Y", Arena, DS 103, 1982 (Box 1)
- Chadwick, Stu, Heavy Rockers, Arena, DS 107, 1982 (Box 1)
- Chadwick, Stu, Making The Team, Arena, DS 118, 1983 (Box 1)
- Chadwick, Stu, Brother To Brother, Arena, DS 122, 1983 (Box 1)
- Chadwick, Stu, Rough Trade, Arena, DS 129, 1983 (Box 2)
- Champion, Mitchell, The Love Rammers, Star Dist., SPADE 126, 1973 (Box 65)
- Chandler, Jeb, The Cocky Students, Star Dist., HS 1011, 1975 (Box 62)
- Channing, Charles, The Randy Reamer, Star Dist., SPADE 142, 1974 (Box 66)
- Charles, Anthony, Prison Punk, Rough Trade, RT 484, 1979 (Box 56)
- Charles, Damian, Slave To His Brother, Star Dist., SS-1028, 1979 (Box 67)
- Charles, Saxby L., Son Comin' Out, Surey Books, SSS 126, 1982 (Box 86)
- Charles, Saxby L., Daddy's Chicken, Surrey House, HIS 69177, 1976 (Box 74)
- Charles, Scott, Jock Lust, Star Dist., SS-1035, 1979 (Box 67)
- Charnot, Gene, New Boy In Town, Surree Ltd, HIS 69405, 1980 (Box 79)
- Choisy, Maryse, A Month Among The Girls, Pyramid Books, G-557, 1960 (Box 53)
- Cholsy, Maryse, A Month Among The Men, Pyramid Books, R-686, 1962 (Box 53)
- Chopping, Richard, The Ring, Bantam Books, 553-05402, 1967 (Box 5)
- Christi, B. F., Jerry's First Love Iii, Star Dist., AGR 169, 1987 (Box 68)
- Clark, Jerry, Danny Does, Gay Parisian Press, GPP 110, 1970 (Box 19)
- Clarke, Otis, Two Way Farm Boy,, ODS/115, 1972 (Box 90)
- Clayton, Hal, Beach Boy Bondage, Greenleaf Classics, AC 192, 1978 (Box 22)
- Cleland, John, Fanny, Olympia Press, no. 17, 1960 (Box 38)
- Clifton, Bud, Muscle Boy, Ace Books, Inc., D-330, 1958 (Box 95)
- Cochran, Bob, Young Wild And Sexy, Gay Parisian Press, GPP 104, 1970 (Box 19)
- Cochran, Bob, School Meat, Surree Ltd, HIS 69169, 1976 (Box 74)
- Cochran, Bob, Crotch Bait, Surrey House, HIS 06906, 1971 (Box 69)
- Cochran, Bob, Easy Come, Surrey House, HIS 06909, 1972 (Box 69)
- Cochran, Bob, Backdoor Seller, Surrey House, HIS 06913, 1972 (Box 69)
- Cochran, Bob, School Meat, Surrey House, HIS 06933, 1972 (Box 70)
- Cochran, Bob, Little Buggers, Surrey House, HIS 06949, 1973 (Box 70)
- Cochran, Bob, Head Giver, Surrey House, HIS 06953, 1973 (Box 70)
- Cochran, Bob, Flood Cumin', Surrey House, HIS 06960, 1973 (Box 70)
- Cochran, Bob, Snow-Job, Surrey House, MH 419, 1973 (Box 81)
- Cochran, Bob, Desert Discovery, XXX Inc., GW 118, 1971 (Box 18)
- Cochran, Bob, Swim Meat, XXX Inc., GW 123, n.d. (Box 18)
- Cochran, Bob, Copsuckers, Surrey House, Inc., HIS6923, 1972 (Box 90)
- Cochran, Morley, The Conqueror, Greenleaf Classics, GL 162, 1970 (Box 26)
- Cocker, Charles, Weak End, GX, Inc., TC 226, n.d. (Box 30)
- Colby, Jim, Trucker's Delight, Parisian Press, P 234, 1972 (Box 42)
- Coleman, Lonnie, Sam, Pyramid Books, F-711, 1959 (Box 53)
- Coles,Todd *, Rough Cons, Rough Trade, RT 458, n.d. (Box 55)
- Colette, Cheri & The Last Of Cheri, Signet Books, S 1189, 1951 (Box 57)
- Collins, Gary, The Sergeant, 101 Enterprises, 101-25, 1968 (Box 40)
- Collins, Hal, Room Service Orgy, Parisian Press, P 218, 1972 (Box 42)
- Colman, Curt, The Latent Lovers, Corinth Pubns., SR 606, 1966 (Box 15)
- Colon, Manuel, Roped & Broken Cowboy, Rough Trade, RT 445, n.d. (Box 55)
- Colson, Frederick, The Devil Is Gay, Brandon House, 933, 1965 (Box 13)
- Colson, Lonnie, Suckin' Truckin' Studs, Surree Ltd, HIS 69197, 1977 (Box 75)
- Colton, James, Lost On Twilight Road, National Library Books, NLB-100, 1964 (Box 36)
- Colton, James, The Outward Side, Olympia Press, TC-506, 1971 (Box 39)
- Colton, James, Todd, Olympia Press, TC-514, 1971 (Box 39)
- Colton, James, Strange Marriage, Argyle Books, 54-371, 1965 (Box 90)
- Colton, James, Cocksure, Greenleaf Classics, GL125, 1969 (Box 93)
- Colton, James, Hang-Up, Brandon House, 3068, 1969 (Box 95)
- Colton, James, Known Homosexual, Brandon House, 2074, 1968 (Box 96)
- Colton, James, The Corrupter (and Other Stories), Greenleaf Classics, GC329, 1968 (Box 96)
- Conners, Pat, Chained By Love, Lavender Publications, -0-, n.d. (Box 34)
- Conrad, Earl, Scottsboro Boy, Bantam Books, 920, 1950 (Box 5)
- Conrad, Earl, Scottsboro Boy, Bantam Books, H2357, 1950 (Box 5)
- Cook, Bill, Gay Teen Boys, Barclay House, 7106, 1970 (Box 6)
- Coolen, Carl, Route 69, 101 Enterprises, -0-, 1968 (Box 40)
- Coolen, Carl, Boy Slaves, 101 Enterprises, 101-16, 1968 (Box 40)
- Coolen, Carl, Ballet For Boys, 101 Enterprises, 101-32, 1968 (Box 40)
- Coop, Sexy Southern Boy, Parisian Press, P 240, 1972 (Box 42)
- Cooper, Bill, Boot Licker, Rough Trade, RT 441, n.d. (Box 55)
- Cooper, Jefferson, Sappho Of Lesbos, Paperback Library, 53-920, 1964 (Box 41)
- Cooper, Raymond, Brother Of The Wind, Blueboy Library, 80037, 1977 (Box 8)
- Cooper, Raymond, Bunk House Hunks, Surree Ltd, MH 489, 1978 (Box 83)
- Cooper, Raymond, Uncle's Hired Hand, Surree Ltd, SS 044, 1978 (Box 85)
- Corbett, Neville, Queer Fear, P. E. C., FL 88, 1970 (Box 52)
- Corey, Moses, Ball Handlers, Timely Books, -0-, 1971 (Box 90)
- Coriolan, John, A Sand Fortress, Universal, A 363N, 1968 (Box 88)
- Coriolan, John, Unzipped, Gay Sunshine Press, -0-, 1983 (Box 93)
- Corley, Carl, Trick Of The Trade, 101 Enterprises, 101-26, 1968 (Box 40)
- Corley, Carl, Swamp Angel, Greenleaf Classics, PR 295, 1971 (Box 46)
- Corley, Carl, Jail Mate, Greenleaf Classics, PR 297, 1971 (Box 46)
- Corley, Carl, Gay Trilogy, P. E. C., Classic 503, 1967 (Box 50)
- Corley, Carl, A Fool's Advice, P. E. C., FL 09, 1967 (Box 50)
- Corley, Carl, Brazen Image, P. E. C., FL 17, 1967 (Box 50)
- Corley, Carl, Sky Eyes, P. E. C., FL 28, 1967 (Box 51)
- Corley, Carl, Jesse-Man Of The Streets, P. E. C., FL 33, 1968 (Box 51)
- Corley, Carl, The Purple Ring, P. E. C., FL 39, 1968 (Box 51)
- Corley, Carl, Cast A Wistful Eye, P. E. C., FL 41, 1968 (Box 51)
- Corley, Carl, Black Angel, P. E. C., FL 47, 1968 (Box 51)
- Corley, Carl, Easy Ride, P. E. C., FL 77, 1970 (Box 52)
- Corley, Carl, My Purple Winter, P. E. C., FL 82, 1970 (Box 52)
- Corley, Carl, Faces In Secret, P. E. C., HES 101, 1967 (Box 53)
- Corley, Carl, The Scarlet Lantern, P. E. C., FL 03, 1966 (Box 50)
- Corley, Carl, My Purple Winter, P. E. C., FL 1, 1966 (Box 50)
- Corley, Carl, Fallen Eagle, P. E. C., FL 11, 1967 (Box 50)
- Corley, Carl, A Lover Mourned, P. E. C., FL 24, 1967 (Box 51)
- Corley, Carl, Satin Chaps, P. E. C., FL 31, 1968 (Box 51)
- Corley, Carl, A Fool's Advice, P. E. C., FL 62, 1969 (Box 52)
- Corley, Carl, A Chosen World, PAD Library, PL 524, 1966 (Box 40)
- Corley, Carl, Star Light Star Bright, PAD Library, PL 537, 1967 (Box 40)
- Corley, Carl, The Hustling Place, Regency, 1027, 1970 (Box 54)
- Corley, Carl, The Purple Ring, Regency, 1032, 1970 (Box 54)
- Cory, John, Learning The Hard Way, Publisher's Consultants, BAB 112, 1978 (Box 49)
- Coulton, James, Gard, Universal Publishing, A541S, 1969 (Box 95)
- Courage, Kevin, Black Pipe Lovers, Big Boy Series, BB-101, n.d. (Box 12)
- Courage, Kevin, Hard, Horny Cowpokes, Rough Trade, RT 447, n.d. (Box 55)
- Courage, Kevin, Man-Handled Men, Rough Trade, RT 448, n.d. (Box 55)
- Courage, Kevin, Hung Hard Head Model, Star Distributors, Ltd., BD-1011, 1976 (Box 90)
- Coxe, Jed, Ride A Hard Cop, Surrey House, MH 407, 1973 (Box 81)
- Coxe, Jed, Hot Load Trucker, Surrey House, MH 418, 1973 (Box 81)
- Coxe, Jed, Peter's Pink, Surrey House, MH 439, 1974 (Box 82)
- Cozad, William, College Stud, Star Dist., AGR 170, 1987 (Box 68)
- Cozad, William, Reamed In Reno, Surey Books, HIS 69560, 1987 (Box 80)
- Cozad, William, Mexican Chicken, Surey Books, HIS 69563, 1987 (Box 80)
- Crandall, Barry, Duet For Two, Echelon, IL-240, 1968 (Box 15)
- Crandall, Barry, Lavender Lads, Echelon, IL-243, 1968 (Box 15)
- Crandall, Barry, The Muscle Swappers, Echelon, IL-328, 1968 (Box 15)
- Crane, Larry, My Dark Lover, Parisian Press, P 207, 1972 (Box 41)
- Crannach, Henry, Flesh And Bone, Olympia Press, no. 38, n.d. (Box 38)
- Cranston, Wes, Mount A Hot Stud, Greenleaf Classics, AC 289, 1982 (Box 23)
- Cranston, Wes, Chicken On The Streets, Greenleaf Classics, AC 301, 1983 (Box 23)
- Cranston, Wes, Oh, Brother Of Mine!, Greenleaf Classics, AC 324, 1984 (Box 23)
- Cray, Ed, The Secret Libertines, Brandon House, 941, 1965 (Box 12)
- Creamum, Carl, Photo Phuck, Surey Books, HIS 69586, 1988 (Box 80)
- Crisp, Quentin, The Naked Civil Servant, Signet Books, E 8292, 1968 (Box 58)
- Cruze, Abel, Sister Sailor, Surrey House, HIS 06907, 1972 (Box 69)
- Cruze, Abel, Ride A Long Horn, Surrey House, HIS 06961, 1973 (Box 70)
- Culver, Ed, Queersville, All Star Books, AS-64, 1965 (Box 1)
- Culver, Ed, Queer Hustler, P. E. C., PL 29, 1967 (Box 51)
- Culver, Ed, Gay Three-Way, P. E. C., N 121, 1966 (Box 53)
- Culver, Ed, Sex Protege, P. E. C., N 128, 1966 (Box 53)
- Culver, Ed, Kept Boy, Rapture Books, RB 408, 1964 (Box 54)
- Cummings, Dale, S-Brother, M-Brother, Surree Ltd, SSS 105, 1981 (Box 86)
- Cummings, Rich, S.U.C.K., Surrey House, HIS 06910, 1972 (Box 69)
- Cummings, Rich, Bath Buddy, Surrey House, HIS 06912, 1972 (Box 69)
- Cummings, Rich, Hotel Dick, Surrey House, HIS 06916, 1972 (Box 69)
- Cummings, Rich, Massage Boy, Surrey House, HIS 06918, 1972 (Box 69)
- Cummings, Rich, Dinging Daddy's Dong, Surrey House, HIS 06921, 1972 (Box 69)
- Cummings, Rich, Kept Boy, Surrey House, HIS 06925, 1972 (Box 69)
- Cummings, Rich, Lip Service, Surrey House, HIS 06935, 1972 (Box 70)
- Cummings, Rich, 10-Inch Toker, Surrey House, HIS 06937, 1972 (Box 70)
- Cummings, Rich, Suck Slave, Surrey House, HIS 06956, 1973 (Box 70)
- Cummings, Rich, A Nice Dick, Surrey House, HIS 06962, 1973 (Box 70)
- Cummings, Rich, Shoot It Out!, Surrey House, HIS 06980, 1974 (Box 71)
- Cummings, Rich, Pay As You Come, Surrey House, MH 404, 1973 (Box 81)
- Cummings, Rich, Buddy's Butt, Surrey House, MH 422, 1973 (Box 81)
- Cummings, Rich, Cockfighters, Surrey House, MH 425, 1973 (Box 81)
- Cummings, Rich, Suckhappy, Surrey House, HIS 06941, 1972 (Box 70)
- Cunningham, Jay, Hard Daddy, Surree House, HIS 69216, 1977 (Box 76)
- Curry, Jim, Show Biz Sucker, Lavender Publications, -0-, n.d. (Box 34)
- Curry, Jim, Leather Tool, Lavender Publications, -0-, n.d. (Box 90)
- Curry, Jim, To the Trade Only, Lavender Publications, -0-, n.d. (Box 90)
- Curtis, Bart, Locker Room Suckers, Star Dist., HS 119, 1975 (Box 62)
- Curtis, Frazer, Come In, Surrey House, HIS 06902, 1971 (Box 69)